David Damerjian Photographs MS155
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
David Damerjian Photographs
1987
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Damerjian, David
MS155
0.25 Linear Feet 1 box
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of eleven 8x10 black and white photographs. David Damerjian, Class of 1988, participated in a photography class in 1987. For this class, he photographed Tufts staff, primarily from Dining Services, and employees of the Hillside Liquor store. These photographs are distinguishable by the use of "Groucho Marx" glasses worn by all the subjects.
Biographical / Historical
David Damerjian, Class of 1988, participated in a photography class in 1987.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Alumni collections
- Photographs, 1987; MS155.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of eleven 8x10 black and white photographs. David Damerjian, Class of 1988, participated in a photography class in 1987. For this class, he photographed Tufts staff, primarily from Dining Services, and employees of the Hillside Liquor store. These photographs are distinguishable by the use of "Groucho Marx" glasses worn by all the subjects.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged as found.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Dining services employee cooking liver, 1987; MS155.001.001.00001; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
    Removed from matte board frame with "liver" written on it.
    Cooks; Dining Services
  - Dining services employee checking in meal tickets, 1987; MS155.001.001.00002; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
    Removed from matte board frame with "meal ticket" written on it.
    Dining Services
  - Dining services employee serving cake, 1987; MS155.001.001.00003; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
    Removed from matte board frame with "cake" written on it.
  - Dining services employee using tongs, 1987; MS155.001.001.00004; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
    Removed from matte board frame with "tongs" written on it.
  - Dining services employee making a salad, 1987; MS155.001.001.00005; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
    Removed from matte board frame with "salad" written on it.
  - Dining services employee with truck and cigarette, 1987; MS155.001.001.00006; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
    Removed from matte board frame with "truck" written on it.
  - Cousens gymnasium security guard at locker, 1987; MS155.001.001.00007; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
    Removed from matte board frame with "guard" written on it.
  - Unidentified male student standing in front of gym locker, 1987; MS155.001.001.00008; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
    Removed from matte board frame with "gym boy" written on it.
  - Facilities worker 'Maurice' with water hose, 1987; MS155.001.001.00009; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
    Removed from matte board frame with "Maurice" written on it.
    Facilities Management
  - Hillside Liquors employee writing, 1987; MS155.001.001.00010; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
  - Hillside Liquors employee at cash register, 1987; MS155.001.001.00011; Damerjian, David (Box 1)
    Removed from matte board frame with "cash register" written on it.